RG 079:001, Department of Environmental Protection: Central Office
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Commissioner, 1957-2004
  - Douglas M. Costle, 1973-1974; 1988-027 (part)
    - Institute of Water Resources (Box 18-7)
    - In-Service Training (Box 18-7)
    - In-o-Ven (Box 18-7)
    - Indian Affairs Council (Box 18-7)
    - IBM Land Transaction (Box 18-7)
    - Information and Education (Box 18-7)
    - White, Susan, Administrative Aide-Office of the Governor (Box 18-7)
    - Stewart, Renee B., Director, Washington, DC, Office of the Governor (Box 18-7)
    - Housatonic Valley Council of Elected Officials (Box 18-7)
    - Housatonic Valley Association (Box 18-7)
    - Hoppers, Bristol (Box 18-7)
    - Herbst, Robert F., Essex Conservation Commission (Box 18-7)
    - Hellier, Sam (Box 18-7)
    - Hearings (Box 18-7)
    - Hartford Times (Box 18-7)
    - Hartford Garage (Box 18-7)
    - Greater Hartford Process (Box 18-7)
    - Lueba, Robert, Executive Assistant to the Governor (Box 18-7)
    - Summary Record of Action (Water Compliance) (Box 18-8)
    - Status Report-Pollution Abatement Programs (Box 18-8)
    - Water and Natural Resources (P & C) (Box 18-8)
    - Barn Island (Wetlands) (Box 18-8)
    - Interstate Water Resource Planning (Box 18-8)
    - Wildlife Biology (Box 18-8)
    - Wetlands Moratorium (Box 18-8)
    - Wetlands Division (Box 18-8)
    - Wetlands Miscellaneous (Box 18-8)
    - Wetlands Thimble Island, Branford (Box 18-8)
    - Action for Clean Air (Box 18-8)
    - Air Compliance (Box 18-8)
    - Air Compliance-Dowd Group (Box 18-8)
    - Connecticut Air Pollution Emergency Plan (Box 18-8)
    - Air Implementation Plan (Box 18-8)
    - Application for Air Pollution Control Program Grant (Box 18-8)
    - Auto Emissions (Box 18-8)
    - Clean Air (Box 18-8)
    - Low Sulfur Fuel Exemptions (Box 18-8)
    - Notice of Plan for Air Quality Control (Box 18-8)
    - Bradley International Airport (Box 18-8)
    - Bridgeport Airport ILS/MLS (Box 18-8)
    - Burning (Box 18-8)
    - Clean Power Symposium, May 13, 1972 (Box 18-8)
    - Connecticut Clean Air Commission (Box 18-8)
    - Cos Cob Power Plant (Box 18-8)
    - Energy-memo from Quentin Riegel re: Energy Survey Questions (Box 18-8)
    - Intra-Department Environmental Quality Division (Box 18-8)
    - Grants (Box 18-8)
    - Gypsy Moth Control (Box 18-8)
    - Hitchcock Chair (Box 18-8)
    - Housing (Box 18-8)
    - Impact Statement-Southern New England Telephone Co. (Box 18-8)
    - Land (Box 18-8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18-8)
    - National Conference on Managing the Environment by D.W. Lufkin (Box 18-8)
    - New England Pollution Control Company (Box 18-8)
    - Norwalk Recycling Plant (Box 18-8)
    - Nuclear Power Plants (Box 18-8)
    - Oil Spills (Box 18-8)
    - Oil Spill Treatment Equipment Brochures-Advertisements (Box 18-8)
    - Outdoor Advertising (Box 18-8)
    - Environmental Quality-Personnel (Box 18-8)
    - Pesticides (Box 18-8)
    - Aerial Spraying (Box 18-8)
    - Planning and Standards (Box 18-8)
    - Quinnipiac River (Box 18-8)
    - Rooster River Flood Control Project (Box 18-8)
    - Radiation Compliance (Box 18-8)
    - Radiation-copy of Letter from Governor to Toby Moffit (Box 18-8)
    - Sewage Disposal Facilities (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Announcement, 1972 July 11 (Box 18-8)
    - Application for Federal Assistance-Solid Waste Programs (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Management Plan (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Proposal Plan (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Proposal Packet (Box 18-8)
    - List of Companies which submitted Solid Waste Proposals (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste-Town of Cheshire (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Compliance (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Authority (Box 18-8)
    - Solid Waste Area Meetings Informational Package, 1973 March 16 (Box 18-8)
    - U.S. Water Resources Council (Box 18-8)
    - Water Compliance (Box 18-8)
    - Water Compliance-Sewers in Branford (Box 18-8)
    - Water Compliance-Sewers in Litchfield (Box 18-8)
    - Water Compliance-Piper Brook Project (Box 18-8)
    - Windsor, Funds for Landfill Operations and Road Costs (Box 18-8)
    - Connecticut Light and Power (Box 18-8)
    - Energy Unlimited Limited-Hartford Civic Centers (Box 18-8)
    - Hartford Electric Light Co. (Box 18-8)
    - Policy, Planning and Research-Energy Crisis (Box 18-8)
    - Northeast Utilities (Box 18-8)
    - Power Companies (Box 18-8)
    - Power Line Crossings (Box 18-8)
    - Power Utilities (Box 18-8)
    - Policy, Planning and Research (Box 18-8)
    - Transportation (Box 18-8)
    - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Box 18-8)
    - Policy, Planning and Research (Box 18-8)
    - Buzzuto, Richard C. (Senate) (Box 18-9)
    - Bond Funds Status Report (Box 18-9)
    - Bond Commission (Box 18-9)
    - Bluff Point (Box 18-9)
    - Beard Construction Company (Box 18-9)
    - B (Box 18-9)
    - Auto Emission Inspection Pilot Program (Box 18-9)
    - Attorney General, Robert K. Killian (Box 18-9)
    - Attorney General, Carl Ajello (Box 18-9)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, Contract (Box 18-9)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 18-9)
    - Ash, Roy L., Director, Office of Management and Budget (Box 18-9)
    - Army Corps of Engineers (Box 18-9)
    - Aquaculture (Box 18-9)
    - Apthrop, Grant B. (Box 18-9)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 18-9)
    - Alwir Construction Company (Box 18-9)
    - Alm, Alvin, Assistant Administrator, EPA (Box 18-9)
    - Altobelli, Dan J., U.S. DOT (Box 18-9)
    - Air Quality Index (Box 18-9)
    - Air Pollution Control Program Grant (Box 18-9)
    - Air Compliance Oxidant Levels (Box 18-9)
    - Air Compliance Regulation (Box 18-9)
    - Air Compliance (Box 18-9)
    - Agricultural Lands Task Force (Box 18-9)
    - Agriculture, Dept. of (Box 18-9)
    - Agostinelli, Nathan, Comptroller (Box 18-9)
    - Ajudication, Office of (Box 18-9)
    - Administration (Box 18-9)
    - Addresses, Lists, and Directories (Box 18-9)
    - Chronological Files, 1974 January-February (Box 18-9)
    - Sulfur Oxides Regulations (Box 18-10)
    - Submerged Lands, Title to (report by Henry Beck) (Box 18-10)
    - Stevens, Gerald F. (Box 18-10)
    - Steele, Robert H. (Box 18-10)
    - State Vehicles (Box 18-10)
    - Spur Report (Box 18-10)
    - Space Requirements (Box 18-10)
    - Solvents Recovery Service of England (Box 18-10)
    - Solid Waste-Secondary Materials (Box 18-10)
    - Solid Waste Operator Training Grant (Box 18-10)
    - Solid Waste Management Advisory Council (Box 18-10)
    - Solid Waste Management (Box 18-10)
    - Solid Waste (Box 18-10)
    - Soil and Water Conservation Districts (Box 18-10)
    - Soil Conservation Service (Box 18-10)
    - Silver Sands (Box 18-10)
    - Shugrue, James F., Acting Commissioner, Department of Transportation (Box 18-10)
    - Sherwood Island (Box 18-10)
    - Sewer Construction Projects (Box 18-10)
    - Septic Code Revers (Box 18-10)
    - Secretary of State, Gloria Schaffer (Box 18-10)
    - Scorp (Box 18-10)
    - Shultz, Robert (4th District Management) (Box 18-10)
    - Telephone (Box 18-10)
    - Telegrams (Box 18-10)
    - Thames River Estuary (Box 18-10)
    - Towns and Cities (Box 18-10)
    - Transportation Controls (Box 18-10)
    - Topsmead (Box 18-10)
    - Telephone Calls Referred (Box 18-10)
    - Tri-State Regional Planning Commission (Box 18-10)
    - Travel Authorization (Box 18-10)
    - United Nations Association of the USA (Box 18-10)
    - University of Connecticut (Box 18-10)
    - Variance-North East Utilities (Box 18-10)
    - Water and Related Resources (Box 18-10)
    - Wolcott Race Track (Box 18-10)
    - WIN (Box 18-10)
    - Wildlife (Box 18-10)
    - Wetlands (Box 18-10)
    - West Rock Ridge State Park (Box 18-10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18-10)
    - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (Box 18-10)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 18-10)
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 18-10)
    - Branford Sewer Funds (Box 18-10)
    - Bottle Bill (Box 18-10)
    - Bradley International Airport (Box 18-10)
    - Bluff Point Report (Box 18-10)
    - Lavine, David, Director (Box 18-11)
    - Lattin’s Cove, Candlewood Lake (Box 18-11)
    - Lansco Inc.-Mycelium (Box 18-11)
    - Land Use (Box 18-11)
    - Land Use Transportation Program (Box 18-11)
    - Land Use Planning (Box 18-11)
    - Clutrap (Box 18-11)
    - Land Use Transportation Program (Box 18-11)
    - King’s Island Windsor Locks Canal (Box 18-11)
    - Kozlowski (Box 18-11)
    - Kellems, Vivian (Box 18-11)
    - Miage Reports (Box 18-11)
    - Vacation Information (Box 18-11)
    - Attendance Report (Box 18-11)
    - Radio Spot-Energy (Box 18-11)
    - Comments re: Sale of State Land (Box 18-11)
    - Governor’s Speech to Connecticut Association of Municipal Attorneys, 1973 October 15 (Box 18-11)
    - Commissioner’s Testimony (Box 18-11)
    - Speeches for Governor Meskill, 1973 September 7 (Box 18-11)
    - Testimony at Council of Environmental Quality, 1973 September 18 (Box 18-11)
    - Briefing Document re: Energy (Box 18-11)
    - Summary of Comments, Nasmi Elo-Technic Workshop in Washington, DC (Box 18-11)
    - Speech at East Hartford Women’s Club, 1973 October 2 (Box 18-11)
    - Murphy, Johanna (Box 18-11)
    - Environmental Education Speech (Box 18-11)
    - Land Use Speech (Box 18-11)
    - Good News/Bad News (Box 18-11)
    - Remarks (Box 18-11)
    - Energy Speech (Box 18-11)
    - Interview with Triple A (Box 18-11)
    - Testimony-Washington, 1974 February 25 (Box 18-11)
    - Testimony-Commissioner Costle (Box 18-11)
    - Statement by Commissioner Costle and David Tunderman (Box 18-11)
    - Governor Meskills Energy Message (Box 18-11)
    - Land Connecticut’s Vanashing Resource (Box 18-11)
    - Remarks of DEP Concerning Noise Pollution Bill, 1974 February 8 (Box 18-11)
    - Testimony on Energy Legislation (Box 18-11)
    - Testimony before Appropriations (Box 18-11)
    - Zalessky Property (Box 18-11)
    - Zajac, John (Senator) (Box 18-11)
    - Youth Conservation Corps. (Box 18-11)
    - Xerox Instructions (Box 18-11)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 18-12)
    - New Rural Society (Box 18-12)
    - New England River Basins Commission (Box 18-12)
    - New England Regional Commission (Box 18-12)
    - New England Power Pool (Box 18-12)
    - Nevas, Alan H. (Representative) (Box 18-12)
    - Natural Resources Defense Council (Box 18-12)
    - Natural Resource Data Center (Box 18-12)
    - Natural Area Preserves Committee (Box 18-12)
    - National Commission on Water Quality (Box 18-12)
    - Metro League of Women Voters (Box 18-12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18-12)
    - Mining (Box 18-12)
    - Miner, Dallas, Connecticut Conservation Association (Box 18-12)
    - Menhaden (Box 18-12)
    - Commissioner’s Memo (Box 18-12)
    - Membership (Box 18-12)
    - Massachusetts Reorganization of Department of Environment (Box 18-12)
    - Maps-Directions (Box 18-12)
    - Map Committee (Box 18-12)
    - Maine Oil Spill Case (Box 18-12)
    - Long Island Sound Study (Box 18-12)
    - Long Island Sound Hearing (Box 18-12)
    - Litter (Box 18-12)
    - Legislative Regulations Review Committee (Box 18-12)
    - Legislative Ethics Committee (Box 18-12)
    - Legislation, 1973 (Box 18-12)
    - Legislative Progress Reports, 1974 (Box 18-12)
    - Legislation, 1974 (Box 18-12)
    - Legislation, 1975 (Box 18-12)
    - Legal Matters (Box 18-12)
    - Noise (Box 18-13)
    - Northeast Utilities System, 10 year Forecast (Box 18-13)
    - Northeast Utilities Variance (Box 18-13)
    - NPDES (Box 18-13)
    - OCS Resource Management Advisory Board (Box 18-13)
    - Offshore Gas and Oil Production (Box 18-13)
    - Oil and Chemical Spill Contingency Plan (Box 18-13)
    - Oil Pollution Skungamaug River (Box 18-13)
    - Old Rock Road (Box 18-13)
    - Orders (Box 18-13)
    - Organizational Chart (DEP) (Box 18-13)
    - OSTAC (Box 18-13)
  - Joseph N. Gill, 1957-1979; 1988-027 (part)
    - Disaster Committee (Box 26-1)
    - Drought Loan Committee Meeting Hotel Bond, 1957 November 4 (Box 26-1)
    - Drought Loans (Box 26-1)
    - Drought Disaster-Hay Program (Box 26-1)
    - Milk Bottle File (Box 26-1)
    - Drought Disaster “Rainmaking” (Box 26-1)
    - U.S. Army Engineer Division New England re: Hurricane Protection (Box 26-1)
    - Upholsterers (Box 26-1)
    - U-V (Box 26-1)
    - WTIC (Box 26-1)
    - W (Box 26-1)
    - Red Cross-Blood Donors-J.N. Gill, 1957 February (Box 26-1)
    - S (Box 26-1)
    - Secretary of State (Box 26-1)
    - T-R (Box 26-1)
    - Requests for Whyte Report (Box 26-1)
    - IBM (Box 26-1)
    - TR 20 (Box 26-1)
    - Computer Program HEC-1, HEC-2, WSP-2, TR 20 (Box 26-1)
    - Legislation-Special Session, 1957 September 17 (Box 26-2)
    - CT State Board of Agriculture re: The Effects of Exempting Farm (Box 26-2)
    - Livestock and Equipment From Property Taxes (Box 26-2)
    - Analysis of the Agriculture Doubt in Connecticut, 1957 (Box 26-2)
    - Dept. of Agriculture (Box 26-2)
  - Stanley J. Pac, 1973-1987
    - Subject Files, 1977-1987; 1988-018
      - Adjudications/Final Decisions F-Z (Box 1)
      - Adjudication General (Box 1)
      - State Adj. General (Box 1)
      - Administration-General (Box 1)
      - Administrative Services (Box 1)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 1)
      - Aging (Box 1)
      - Agriculture (Box 1)
      - Air Compliance (Box 1)
      - Air Emissions (Box 1)
      - American Cyanamid (Box 4)
      - American Shakespeare Theatre (Box 4)
      - Amicus Journal (Box 4)
      - Annual Report (Box 4)
      - Ansonia (Box 4)
      - Appalachian Trailways (Box 4)
      - Appropriations Commission (Box 4)
      - Agriculture (Box 4)
      - Aquifer-Studies (Box 4)
      - Army Corps of Engineers (Box 4)
      - Arson Resource (Box 4)
      - Asbestos (Box 4)
      - Asst. Chief State’s Attorney (DEP) (Box 4)
      - Atlantic Alliance (Box 4)
      - A (miscellaneous) (Box 5)
      - Acid Rain, 1981-1985 (Box 5)
      - Adjudications/Final Decisions A-E (Box 5)
      - Attorney General (Box 6)
      - Audit CPEP (Box 6)
      - Avery Brook Watershed (Box 6)
      - Avon (Box 6)
      - B (Miscellaneous) (Box 6)
      - Bantam Lake (Box 6)
      - Barkhamsted (Box 6)
      - Beach Erosion (Box 6)
      - Beacon Falls (Box 6)
      - Bear Mountain (Salisbury) (Box 6)
      - Berlin (Box 6)
      - Bi-Weekly Staff Reports (Box 6)
      - Blood Service (Box 6)
      - Bluff Point (Box 6)
      - Board of Higher Education (Box 6)
      - Boat Ramps (Box 6)
      - Bradley Field (Box 6)
      - Branford (Box 6)
      - Bridgeport (Box 6)
      - Bristol Landfill (Sewer) (Box 6)
      - Bristol Myers (Box 6)
      - Brookfield (Sewer) (Box 6)
      - Brooklyn (Box 6)
      - Brun-Del Corp (Southington) (Box 6)
      - BTU Bubble (Box 6)
      - Budget (DEP) (Box 6)
      - Bureau of Land Management (Box 6)
      - Boating (Box 6)
      - Boating Accidents (Box 6)
      - Bolton (Box 6)
      - Bond Requests (Box 6)
      - Bottle Bill (Box 6)
      - Bottled Water (Box 6)
      - Bozrah (Box 6)
      - Building Working Conditions (Heat) (Box 6)
      - Chronological Files, 1981-1986 (Box 7)
      - House Bills (Box 7)
      - Senate Bills (Box 7)
      - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 39)
      - Camping (Box 39)
      - Canaan Airport (Box 39)
      - Canada (Box 39)
      - Candlewood Lake (Box 39)
      - Carcinogenic (Box 39)
      - CPR (Box 39)
      - CEIP (Box 39)
      - Century Brass (Box 39)
      - Charter Oak Passes (Box 39)
      - Chatfield Hallow St. Park (Box 39)
      - Child Care Facility (Box 39)
      - Citizens Advisory Council (Box 39)
      - Citizens Bulletin (Box 39)
      - Citizens Crime Commission (Box 39)
      - Civil Preparedness (Box 39)
      - Claims Commission (Box 39)
      - Clean Air Act (Box 39)
      - Clean Water Fund (Box 39)
      - Coal Conversion (Box 39)
      - Coastal Embankment Advisory Board (Box 39)
      - Coastal Area Management (Box 39)
      - Coastal Area Management Advisory Board (Box 43)
      - Colchester Hampton Sewers (Box 43)
      - Colchester, Town of (Box 43)
      - Colchester Landfill (Box 43)
      - Coleman Brothers Show, Inc. (Box 43)
      - Combined Health Appeal (Box 43)
      - Combustion Equipment Assoc. (Box 43)
      - Commercial Dept. (Box 43)
      - Commission on the Arts (Box 43)
      - Communications (DEP) (Box 43)
      - Compo Cove Erosion (Box 43)
      - Comptroller’s Office (Box 43)
      - CONES (Coalition of North East Governors) (Box 43)
      - Conference/Meeting Rooms, S.O.B. (Box 43)
      - CT Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 43)
      - CT Agriculture Experiment Station (Box 43)
      - CACIWC (Box 43)
      - CT Association of Soil and Water Conservation (Box 43)
      - CT Audubon Society (Box 43)
      - CT’s 350th Birthday (Box 43)
      - CT Board of Higher Education (Box 43)
      - CT Business and Industry Association (Box 43)
      - CTC Results and Sampling (Box 43)
      - CT Chemical Corp, Bristol (Box 43)
      - CCAG CT Citizens Action (Box 43)
      - CT Conference of Municipalities (Box 43)
      - CT Council of Diving Clubs (Box 43)
      - CT Employees Union (Box 43)
      - CT Energy Advisory Board (Box 43)
      - CEPED (Box 43)
      - CT Environmental Caucus (Box 43)
      - CT Environmental Mediation Center (Box 43)
      - CT Environmental Policy Act (Box 43)
      - CT Farm Bureau (Box 43)
      - CT Forests and Parks (Box 43)
      - CT Fund for Environment (Box 43)
      - CT Hazardous Waste Management (Box 43)
      - CT Historical Commission (Box 43)
      - CT Horse Council (Box 43)
      - CT Land and Water Conservation Fund (Box 43)
      - CT Lung Association (Box 43)
      - CT Marine Trade Association (Box 43)
      - CHEEC (Box 43)
      - CT National Guard (Box 43)
      - Connecticut River Assembly (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Gateway Commission (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Race (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Study Water Resources (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Valley Flood Control (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Water Diversion (Box 40)
      - Connecticut River Watershed Council (Box 40)
      - Connecticut Siting Council (Box 40)
      - Connecticut Solid and Hazardous Waste Siting Commission (Box 40)
      - Council of Environmental Quality (Box 40)
      - Council on Soil and Water Conservation (Box 40)
      - Coventry Landfill (Box 40)
      - Construction Grants (Box 40)
      - Consulting Firms (Box 40)
      - Consumer Protection (Box 40)
      - PCB’s Meeting, 1985 August (Box 40)
      - Consumer Protection (Box 40)
      - Conyers Farm (Box 40)
      - Cooks’ Dam (Box 40)
      - Cooperative River Basin Study (Box 40)
      - Corrections Dept. (Box 40)
      - CRRA, 1982 January - 1985 July (Box 8)
      - CPTA-Current Year (Box 22)
      - CT Public Transportation System (Box 22)
      - CT Recreation and Park Association (Box 22)
      - CT Resources Recovery Authority (Box 22)
      - CT Natural Area Reserves Program (Box 22)
      - CT Petroleum Council (Box 22)
      - CT Resources Recovery Authority (Box 22)
      - CT Treatment Corp. (Box 9)
      - CT Urban Action Task Force (Box 9)
      - Conservation Commission (Box 9)
      - Conservation Officers (Box 9)
      - Conservation and Protection (Box 9)
      - Disposal (Box 9)
      - Crystal Mall (Box 41)
      - D9 (Miscellaneous) (Box 41)
      - Dams (Box 41)
      - Danbury, City of (Box 41)
      - Day Pond (Box 41)
      - Deer (Box 41)
      - Delegation letters (Box 41)
      - DEP Reorganization Plans (Box 41)
      - Derby, Town of (Box 41)
      - Designation of Agents (Box 41)
      - DEP Achievements (Box 41)
      - Dinosaur State Park (Box 41)
      - Dioxin (Box 41)
      - Directives (Box 41)
      - Dredging (Box 41)
      - Drinking Water (Box 41)
      - Drought (Box 41)
      - E (Miscellaneous) (Box 41)
      - Eagleville Dam (Box 41)
      - Eastern Lands and Resources (Box 41)
      - Eastern States Expo (Box 41)
      - East Hampton Sewer Project (Box 41)
      - East Hartford, City of (Box 41)
      - East Haven Landfill (Box 41)
      - East Lyme, Town of (Box 41)
      - Economic Development (Box 41)
      - Education Dept. (Box 41)
      - Electric Cars (Box 10)
      - Elm St. Cheese Co., Inc. (Box 10)
      - Elmco, Brookfield, CT (Box 10)
      - Emergency Call List-DEP (Box 10)
      - Emergency Response Commission (Box 10)
      - Emery Worldwide (Box 10)
      - Energy (Box 10)
      - Energy-Advisory Board (Box 10)
      - Enfield/East Windsor (Box 10)
      - Environmental 2000 (Box 10)
      - Environmental (Box 10)
      - Environmental Achievements (70-80) (Box 10)
      - Environmental and Energy Study Institute (Box 10)
      - Environmental Committee Legislation (Box 10)
      - Environmental Health Commissioners of New England (Box 10)
      - Environmental Protection Department (Box 10)
      - EPA (Federal) (Box 10)
      - Environmental Quality-General (Box 10)
      - Environmental Quality-Current Year (Box 10)
      - Environmental Quality-Previous Year (Box 10)
      - ERT Environment Review Team (Box 10)
      - EPA-Weekly Report (Box 10)
      - Equestrian Center Implementation Commission (Box 10)
      - Erosion-water resources (Box 10)
      - Essex, Town of (Box 10)
      - Ethics Commission (Box 10)
      - Executive Order #18 (Box 10)
      - EWR- Lab Reports, 1982 September (Box 10)
      - Environmental Waste Removal, Waterbury (Box 10)
      - Environmental Waste Removal Sampling Results (Box 10)
      - Alpha F (Box 3)
      - Fairfield (Town of) Mill River (Box 3)
      - Farm River Flood Control Project (Box 3)
      - Farmington River Diversion (Box 3)
      - Farmington River Water Shed Committee (Box 3)
      - FEMA (also Civil Preparedness) (Box 3)
      - Federal Paper Board (Box 3)
      - Federal Water Pollution Control Act (Box 3)
      - Fire Safety (Box 3)
      - Fiscal Year-Following (Box 3)
      - Fiscal Year-Current (Box 3)
      - Fish and Wildlife (Box 3)
      - Fisheries Unit (Box 3)
      - Flex Time (Box 3)
      - DEP Inland Flooding Emergency Operations Manual (Box 3)
      - Flood Damage (Box 3)
      - Flood, Storms, 1982 (Box 3)
      - Fly problems/also poultry (Box 11)
      - Forest and Park Association, Inc., CT (Box 11)
      - Forestry-current and previous year (Box 11)
      - Forestry-fuel wood/fire wood (Box 11)
      - Formal DEHYDE (Box 11)
      - Fort Griswold (Box 11)
      - Franklin, Town of (Box 11)
      - Freedom of Information (Box 11)
      - Fresh Air Fund (Box 11)
      - Frito-Lay (Killingly) (Box 11)
      - Futures-The Commission of CT Futures (Box 11)
      - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 11)
      - Gardner Lake (Box 11)
      - Gasoline Allocation (Box 11)
      - Gateway Commission (Box 11)
      - General Assembly Acts, Resolution (Box 11)
      - General Dynamics (Box 11)
      - Gillette Castle (Box 11)
      - Glasgo Dam (Box 11)
      - Glastonbury, Town of (Box 11)
      - Globescope II (Box 11)
      - Gorton Lake Shore Association (Box 11)
      - Gold, Martin D., Executive Asst (Box 11)
      - Governor Advisory Commission, A-K (Box 12)
      - Governor’s Draft Responses (Box 13)
      - Governor’s Correspondence-Current Year (Box 13)
      - Governor’s Office-General Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Governor’s Horse Guard (Box 13)
      - Granby, Town of (Box 13)
      - Green House Effect (Box 13)
      - Groton Sewer Outfall (Box 13)
      - Groundwater Contamination (Box 13)
      - Gypsy Moth (Box 13)
      - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 13)
      - Haddam, Town of (Box 13)
      - Haley Farm State Park (Box 13)
      - Hamden, CT (Box 13)
      - Mammonaseh (Box 13)
      - Hancock Brook Firing Range (Box 13)
      - Harkness Memorial (Box 13)
      - Hartford Riverfront (Box 13)
      - Hartland, Town of (Box 13)
      - Hazardous Air Pollution Advisory Panel (Box 13)